<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Fiftytwo Plus One</title>
    <link>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Fiftytwo Plus One</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:51:05 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Week 05</title>
      <link>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week05/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 20:51:05 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week05/</guid>
      <description>Busy Days I&amp;rsquo;ve had a particularly busy week at work. That said, I&amp;rsquo;ve stil managed to make some progress in my game.&#xA;Although if I am being honest, it&amp;rsquo;s quite frustrating seeing how little progress I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to make.&#xA;In these times, I try to remember and look back to see how far I&amp;rsquo;ve traveled. And although it doesn&amp;rsquo;t totally resolve the frustration, it&amp;rsquo;s enough to reduce the intensity.&#xA;Game Updates This past week and some-odd days saw me focus on AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 04</title>
      <link>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:56:25 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week04/</guid>
      <description>Brains Are Weird I am typing this post on my new split ergonomic keyboard and man am I having a hell of a time. That previous sentence took me over a minute to write.&#xA;Given the new layout of the keyboard, I suddenly feel as if my brain is getting muscle cramps. I keep feeling the battle between my muscle memory, gliding my fingers to where they &amp;ldquo;should&amp;rdquo; go and the unexpected jolt of seeing an unexpected character show up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 03</title>
      <link>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 21:25:19 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week03/</guid>
      <description>Technically Still Counts Well this post is a tad (5 days) late. That said, I&amp;rsquo;m still keeping to the 1 post a week schedule! Also changing the overall structure of this an all foreseeable future posts. Going to start with the gaming updates and then get into personal thoughts Here we go!&#xA;Game Progress I&amp;rsquo;ve worked through several &amp;ldquo;features&amp;rdquo; since the last post. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot going on here, so let me break it down.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 02</title>
      <link>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week02/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 19:46:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week02/</guid>
      <description>Why am I like this? You know, it&amp;rsquo;s funny. I was unemployed for more than half the year in 2023.&#xA;During that time, I had ample freedom to do whatever I wanted, and by god if working on Unreal wasn&amp;rsquo;t something on my mind everyday. But that&amp;rsquo;s just it - it was merely on my mind. Mostly serving as some kind of fiendish reminder of my inability to do what I know I can and should.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 01</title>
      <link>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week01/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2024 20:58:44 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/week01/</guid>
      <description>Hitting the Ground Crawling This post is late due to work related delays (in the future I&amp;rsquo;ll have something out each Sunday), but I&amp;rsquo;m commited to writing a post a week so here&amp;rsquo;s me shoehorning one in.&#xA;Game Still not totally sure on what the game will be, but at this point my goal is to get a character that can shoot set up. High level next step would be to set up enemies that the player can affect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Week 00</title>
      <link>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 17:23:09 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://fiftytwoplusone.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Something something new beginnings&amp;hellip; The intention of this blog is to mainly serve as a way for me to keep myself on track this year for my game development efforts. While I don&amp;rsquo;t have a detailed fleshed goals for this year (yet), I know that spending a meaningful amount of time on game development will be one of them.&#xA;Each post will provide an update about the progress I&amp;rsquo;ve made in the past week both at a high level, and if encountering something particularly interesting during development, likely involve a deeper techincal dive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
